https://www.modrall.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy This Privacy Statement outlines the information we may collect through use of this website (“Modrall Sperling Site”) and how such information may be used and disclosed. We do not collect personally identifiable information (PII) through the Modrall Sperling Site unless such information is provided to us by e-mail via a link contained on the Modrall Sperling Site. It is important to note that any such communications are subject to the Terms of Use for the Modrall Sperling Site.This website uses cookies, text files that are placed on your computer to allow your computer to be recognized by our website so that we may analyze how the site is being used. This analysis of compiled aggregate and statistical information may include number of visitors, how visitors find their way to our website, total time spent on our website, and the pages they visit, is gathered so that we are better able to keep our website content relevant to our readers.The cookies on our website may be used by third-party web analytics services, such as Google Analytics. Modrall Sperling has taken the added precaution on our readers’ behalf to automatically anonymize all IP addresses.We also collect the personal data you provide to us directly. This information is typically provided in one of two ways:From visitors who have opted-in to receive communications from Modrall Sperling such as invitations to our seminars and events, or to send out newsletters or other news relating to our firm and/or the areas of our practice where the visitor has indicated a specific interest.From visitors who choose to email an attorney from our website. Visitors who click a link to open an email form will notice a separate disclaimer and a form for explicit consent. While the email does not immediately begin a client-attorney relationship, personal data is necessary for conducting the business for which the individual has initiated contact, e. g., responding to an inquiry or, should both the visitor and Modrall Sperling agree to work together, for engaging in regard to the matter of interest.Individuals who subscribe to receive newsletters, alerts and invitations can withdraw at any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” button at the bottom of every news item we send. Please be aware that once a reader has unsubscribed, we are unable to re-instate that individual’s account for future communications. We will not attempt to link or match the anonymous technical information we collect with any personally-identifiable information or disclose to third parties personally identifiable information collected by us through the Modrall Sperling Site unless:We have your consentWe (or our service providers) have detected or reasonably suspect any attempt to damage the Modrall Sperling Site or other security breach, orWe are required by law to do soPermanent cookies are stored indefinitely on a user’s hard drive unless manually deleted, while temporary cookies are automatically deleted from the user’s browser upon logging out of a web site.Web browsers typically allow users to disable permanent and/or temporary cookies. The foregoing policy is effective as of May 25, 2018. Modrall Sperling reserves the right to change this policy at any time. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact info@modrall.com. Latest NewsDecember 8, 2020  |  Alerts, Articles, NewsModrall Sperling COVID-19 Task Force – Updated December 3, 2020December 7, 2020  |  AlertsNew Mexico’s Conditional Certification of EPA’s Proposed Reissuance of the Multi Sector General Permit for Stormwater Discharges Associated with Industrial Activity Raises Significant ConcernsDecember 7, 2020  |  AlertsNew Mexico Oil Conservation Commission adopts rule changes concerning produced waterPracticesIndustriesAttorneysNewsContactFind an Attorney
A B C D E F G H I J K L M N O P Q R S T U V W X Y Z
PracticeBankruptcy and Creditors’ RightsCorporate, Business and FinanceBanking and LendingEntity Formation and GovernancePrivate Equity and Venture CapitalPublic FinanceEnergy, Environment and Natural ResourcesAir QualityCultural and Historic ResourcesEnergyEnvironmentMiningOil and GasPipelines and TransmissionPublic LandsRenewable EnergyUtilities and InfrastructureWastes / Contaminated PropertiesWater Rights and Water QualityGovernment RelationsLabor, Employment and BenefitsLitigationAlternative Dispute ResolutionAntitrustAppellateClass Actions and Mass TortsCommercialInsuranceProduct LiabilityProfessional LiabilityTorts / Personal InjuryNative American LawEconomic DevelopmentEnergy and ResourcesTribal Law and CourtsReal EstateTaxationTrusts and Estates
IndustryBusiness in Indian CountryConstruction and DesignEducational Services and InstitutionsEnergyFinancial ServicesHealthcare / Senior Care FacilitiesManufacturingMiningNonprofit / Tax-Exempt OrganizationsRailroadsRanching and Agriculture
Office LocationAlbuquerqueSanta Fe
Bar AdmissionAlabamaArizonaCaliforniaColoradoIsleta Tribal CourtMichiganNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaTexasThe Navajo NationU.S. Bankruptcy Court for the District of New MexicoU.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia CircuitU.S. Court of Appeals for the Ninth CircuitU.S. Court of Appeals for the Sixth CircuitU.S. Court of Appeals for the Tenth CircuitU.S. Court of Federal ClaimsU.S. District Court for the Central District of CaliforniaU.S. District Court for the District of ColoradoU.S. District Court for the District of New MexicoU.S. District Court for the District of North DakotaU.S. District Court for the District of UtahU.S. District Court for the Eastern District of MichiganU.S. District Court for the Middle District of North CarolinaU.S. District Court for the Northern District of OklahomaU.S. District Court for the Western District of OklahomaU.S. District Court for the Western District of TexasU.S. Tax CourtUnited States Supreme CourtUtahWashington DCWisconsin
Law SchoolAlbany Law SchoolArizona State University Sandra Day O’Conner College of LawBaylor University School of LawBoston College Law SchoolBoston University School of LawBrooklyn Law SchoolCreighton University School of LawDePaul University College of LawEmory University School of LawFordham UniversityGeorgetown University Law CenterGeorgia State UniversityHarvard University Law SchoolLoyola Law SchoolLoyola University Chicago School of LawNew York UniversitySamford UniversitySouthern Methodist University Dedman School of LawUniversity of ArizonaUniversity of California at Los AngelesUniversity of California‘s Hastings College of LawUniversity of Chicago School of LawUniversity of Florida Levin College of LawUniversity of Michigan Law SchoolUniversity of New Mexico School of LawUniversity of Texas School of LawUniversity of VirginiaUniversity of Wisconsin Law School
View All Attorneys
